weddingsutra.com 2013-06-30

# WeddingSutra.com – Leading Resource on Indian Weddings.

**WeddingSutra's Privacy Policy >> **  

WeddingSutra is strongly committed to your right to privacy. Keeping this in mind we have formulated a privacy policy to inform you about the information we collect, why we do so and how we use the same. 

**How We Collect Information**  
As many of you would be aware, the way in which you interact with our site, enables us to learn a lot about you. WeddingSutra collects and stores statistics, other information about the online activities of our visitors on an aggregated (collective) basis. We log IP addresses for system administration, troubleshooting, and to examine overall traffic trends. However, we do not obtain personally identifiable information about the visitors. 

In some instances where we ask for personally identifiable information, you have the option of choosing to reveal it to us or to one of the vendors in our Network. Examples of when you voluntarily submit this kind of information include your responses to some of our polls, your participation in sweepstakes or contests, your entry on our registration pages, your feedback and responses in our chat rooms or message boards. 

**How We Use and Disclose Your Information**  
The information we collect from you would enable us to further improve on our content, customize the content in certain pages and keep in touch with you via updates. WeddingSutra does share information such as names, postal addresses and demographic information with other pre-screened organizations who have specific direct mail product and service offers which in our opinion, may be of interest to you. However, you may choose to remove your name and address from the mailing lists which we provide to these other companies. 

**Additional information about online privacy and changes to our policy**   
Please be aware that on our site we have advertisements and links to other websites that may collect personal information about you. This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices or policies of such websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of all such sites, as their policies may be materially different from our Privacy Policy. Any material changes in the way we use personal information will be described in future versions of this Privacy Policy.
